<u>OBJECTIVE:</u> PHP (LARAVEL FRAMEWORK) Developer with 3 year of experience in building PHP Websites. Possess a B.Tech. in Computer Science. Aspiring for a challenging career in Software Development as to use my learned skills and experience for best results.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

- ➤ Working as PHP Developer at **Velocis Systems Pvt ltd.** From Jan 2019 –Till Date
- ➤ Worked as PHP Developer in **Smart Matrix Pvt. Ltd**. From Jan 2018 to Jan 2019
- Worked as a intern in WebTek Labs Pvt. Ltd. from may 2015 to july 2015 and in Ducat Ghaziabad from jan 2015 to Dec 2015

EDUCATION:

➤ B. Tech from SUNDAR DEEP ENGINEERING COLLEGE in year 2012-2016 with Computer Science (70%)

SKILLS SET:

Front End: HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap, AJAX, JQuery (3.3.1).

Back End: PHP Framework Laravel 5.6

IDE: Notepad++, Sublime Text.

Database: MySQL

PROJECTS IN VELOCIS SYSTEMS PVT. LTD

Project Name: SUVIDHA

Description: Laravel, MySQL, AJAX, JQuery.

https://suvidha.eci.gov.in

Description & Responsibilities:

The Election Commission of India is working towards easing Candidates procedure for filing nomination and permission during the election period. The nomination and permission is filed through web application namely SUVIDHA, application has two main module

- Nomination: Candidate can view the status of his nomination. The candidate has an option to view the affidavit and receipt.
- ➤ **Permission:** Here a candidate may view the details of permissions request filed by himself. The permission status and total count is displayed in this section.

Project Name: RTI

Description: Laravel, MySQL, AJAX, JQuery.

https://rti.eci.nic.in

Description & Responsibilities:

Election Commission of India (ECI) had envisaged about an Online Portal where Indian citizens can file RTI applications and appeals directly to ECI under Right to Information ACT, 2005. This RTI Online Portal would facilitate citizens of India to obtain information they want from ECI. There are four modules

- > Citizen: Citizens can file RTI applications and appeals directly to ECI.
- **Nodal:** Forward the citizen applications to their respective CPIO.
- > CPIO:CPIO reply to citizens application.
- First Appeal:If Citizen not satisfied with CPIO reply can Apply for Appeal.

PROJECT DEVELOPED IN LARAVEL FRAMEWORK

Description: Laravel, MySQL, AJAX, JQuery.

- > https://www.delhismartcities.com
- https://www.ddalzoneprojects.com
- https://www.dwarkalzoneconsultants.com

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: 2/8/1993

Languages known: Hindi, English

Current Address: Ghaziabad, Uttar pradesh

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above mentioned information is true to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for any incorrectness, if found in the above data.

(Soni Maurya)